=== Global Flash Gallery ===
Contributors: global-flash-galleries
Author Homepage: http://flash-gallery.com/
Donate link: http://flash-gallery.com/wordpress-plugin
Tags: photo, images, pictures, flash, gallery, slideshow, media, photos, image, post, page, flip, plugin, admin, posts, picture, album, portfolio, presentation, widget
Requires at least: 2.9
Tested up to: 3.0.10
Stable tag: 0.7.11

In Global Flash Gallery plugin we joined several galleries that can be operated from a single shell.  

== Description ==

Global Flash Gallery plugin can help you to create fast and perfectly wonderful and unique galleries of great albums, photos, cards and other images. 

Global Flash Galleries plugin is easy and convenient for use. It's captivating and beautiful to execute in practice. Ready-made harmonic color layouts are offered in this plug-in. 
It is possible to preview a gallery created from several albums in a convenient mode of slide show (full size) or in thumbnails (streaming tape). It's easy with Global Flash Galleries to create different galleries from numerous grouped albums even if you don't have much experience in it. 
There are many various and apprehensible settings and styles with which you can easily change the size of images preserving its original proportion and put the required tags. The plug-in navigation is made at the highest levels and has a broad range of demonstration effects which are easy and plain to comprehend. The excellent functional capabilities of the plug-in will help to create a really peculiar and distinctive collection of galleries.

Please find in the Screenshots section the short descriptions of every gallery.

<a href='http://flash-gallery.com/wordpress-plugin/' title='Wordpress Gallery Plugin Demo'>Demo</a>

0.7.11

* Wordpress 3.0.10 compatibility

0.7.10

* Multisite mode support
* Fixed bug with repeating of the images captions
* Wordpress 3.0.5 compatibility

0.7.9

* Zen gallery: added options for internationalization
* Ability to work on HTTPS hosts
* Wordpress 3.0.4 compatibility

0.7.6

* Wordpress 3.0.1 compatibility

0.7.5

* Fix minor bugs

0.7.4

* Fix some bugs

0.7.1

* Wordpress 3.0 compatibility

0.6.12

* Fix some bugs

0.6.11

* Correct work with PHP4

0.6.10

* Optimisation "Manage Galleries" page for the faster loading

0.6.9

* Add new 3D wall gallery

0.6.8.1

* Add Flash Gallery Widget (for WordPress 2.8 and higher only)

0.6.7

* Fix bug with the link in PhotoFlow gallery

0.6.6

* New version of flash galleries
* New Box Gallery parameter: Drop Shadow
* Limitation for maximum pictures size to 2880?2880 (2800?1440 for PhotoFlow)

0.6.4

* You can add albums to the Zen gallery
* Fix time bug
* Correct parameters saving, when you change gallery type

0.6.2

* Add new galleries
* Fix some bugs

0.5.4

* Fix some bugs

0.5.3

* Export XML file with gallery settings 

0.5.2

* Fix some bugs

0.5.1

* You can add link to the images
* Fix some bugs

0.4.7

* Fix some bugs

0.4.6

* WP 2.9.2 compatibility
* Fix some bugs

0.4.5

* Correct big image uploading
* Fix some bugs

0.4.4

* Now you can upload images with archive
* Fix bug with gallery display on some hosting
* Add some warnings

0.4.1

* PHP4 support

0.4.0

* Add "Load images from URL" function
* Transparent preview
* Fixed some bugs

Features:

* Several Flash Galleries
* Upload Images from FTP folder
* Easy Navigation mode 
* Managment of the galleries is simple (AJAX based)
* Upload Images: Batch upload, upload from URL, Upload Zip-file

== Installation ==

This Global Flash Galleries plugin is simple to install and can be done in a matter of minutes. The following steps will guide you through the process:

1. Unpack the *.zip file and extract the /global-flash-galleries/ folder.
2. Using an FTP program, upload the /global-flash-galleries/ folder to your WordPress plugins directory (Example: /wp-content/plugins/).
3. Open your WordPress Admin panel and go to the 'Plugins' page. Locate the 'FlippingBook gallery' plugin and click on the 'Activate' link.
4. If you need help, review the http://flash-gallery.com/support/

== Frequently Asked Questions ==

Please read these [FAQs] http://flash-gallery.com/support/

== Support ==

http://flash-gallery.com/contacts/

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

Copyright 2008-2010 Flash Gallery Team

== Screenshots ==

1. Flash Gallery sample
2. Flash Gallery sample
3. Flash Gallery sample
4. Flash Gallery sample
5. Flash Gallery sample